<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Kart</string>
    <string name="bollywood_movies">Bollywood Movies</string>
    <string name="hollywood_movies">Hollywood Movies</string>
    <string name="anime_movies">Anime Movies</string>
    <string name="recent_added">Recent Added</string>
    <string name="view_all">VIEW ALL</string>
    <string name="title_activity_movie_detail">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"


        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"


        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="category">
        <item>"---Select Category---"</item>
        <item>"Bollywood"</item>
        <item>"Hollywood"</item>
        <item>"South-Dub"</item>
        <item>"Anime Movie(sub)"</item>
        <item>"Anime Movie(dub)"</item>
        <item>"Anime Marathon(sub)"</item>
        <item>"Anime Marathon(dub)"</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movie_type">
        <item>"---Select type---"</item>
        <item>"bollywood"</item>
        <item>"hollywood"</item>
        <item>"anime"</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
